{
    "subject": "June_Diane_Raphael",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Paul_Scheer",
    "human_readable": "June Diane Raphael is married to Paul Scheer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9867584109306335,
            "question": "Is there a known marriage between June Diane Raphael and Paul Scheer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9686380624771118,
            "question": "Who is June Diane Raphael married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9568416476249695,
            "question": "Name the spouse of June Diane Raphael."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.955979585647583,
            "question": "To whom is June Diane Raphael currently married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9346596598625183,
            "question": "Are June Diane Raphael and Paul Scheer in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.879118800163269,
            "question": "Who are Paul Scheer and June Diane Raphael?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7027409076690674,
            "question": "What is the name of Paul Scheer's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6943315267562866,
            "question": "Is June Diane Raphael in a committed partnership?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6683274507522583,
            "question": "Who shares a marital bond with June Diane Raphael?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3514474034309387,
            "question": "What is the name of Paul Scheer's significant other?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=June Diane Raphael is married to Paul Scheer.",
            "html": "yago_16037_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who shares a marital bond with June Diane Raphael?",
            "html": "yago_16037_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is June Diane Raphael in a committed partnership?",
            "html": "yago_16037_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Paul Scheer's wife?",
            "html": "yago_16037_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16037_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16037_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16037_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16037_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16037_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16037_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16037_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16037_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16037_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16037_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text provides several confirmations that June Diane Raphael and Paul Scheer are married, including details about their wedding date, children, and co-hosted podcast.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that June Diane Raphael and Paul Scheer have been married since October 10, 2009. Therefore, the statement \"June Diane Raphael is married to Paul Scheer\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}